#### Contact

daisyjmuro@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/daisyjmuro (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Data Entry

Bilingual

ECG & Pharmacology

### Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Hospital Fire and Life Safety

Registered Nurse

ECG and Pharmacology

### Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau - Honors Society of Nursing

Honors Recognition

Mentorship Program

# Daisy Muro, BSN, RN, PHN

Registered Nurse at Kaiser Permanente

Los Angeles Metropolitan Area

### Summary

Enthusiastic, charismatic, and bilingual Kaiser Permanente nurse. I am excited for this opportunity and the beginning of a new chapter in life. I graduated and obtained my BSN from West Coast University and my CA RN license soon after. I have over 10 years of customer service experience and I reflect that in my patient care. I am a single mom that has fulfilled her dream of becoming a nurse.

## Experience

Kaiser Permanente Registered Nurse February 2020 - Present (7 months)

Lakewood Regional Medical Center
Student Nurse Worker
July 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 6 months)
Student Nurse Worker
(ED, ICU, CCU, Med Surg, Tele, and Ortho units)

Northeast Community Clinics Medical Assistant/Licensed Phlebotomist 2014 - 2016 (2 years)

Medical Assistant/Licensed Phlebotomist

Pachanga City Mex Cashier 2014 - 2014 (less than a year)

Tireco, Inc General Office Clerk/Receptionist/Cash Apps Clerk 2010 - 2014 (4 years)

General Office Clerk/Receptionist/Cash Applications Clerk

McDonald's Cashier 2007 - 2010 (3 years)

## Education

West Coast University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2016 - 2019)

### **AUMT**

CPT1/Licensed Phlebotomist · (2015 - 2016)

American Career College

Medical Assistant, Medical/Clinical Assistant (2014 - 2014)

Long Beach Polytechnic High School High School Diploma · (2006 - 2010)